samsungchaton.com 2012-05-31

# Samsung account

﻿Samsung Privacy Policy  
This privacy policy applies to the Find My Mobile service hosted at www.samsungdive.com (the "Website") and other online and mobile environments (collectively, the "Service"). The Service is operated by or on behalf of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd, whose principal place of business is at 416 Maetan-3dong, Yeongtong-gu, Suwon-si, Gyeonggi-do, 443-742 Korea ("Samsung", "we" and "us"). This policy applies to personally identifiable information about you which is collected by us through the Service.  
This policy sets out how we use any personally identifiable information about you that you give to us or that we otherwise collect through your use of the Service. If you have any questions or comments in relation to this policy, please contact our customer services department at the Help menu of the Website. Please read this privacy policy carefully. Your use of the Service indicates that you have read, accepted and unconditionally agreed to the privacy practices outlined in this privacy policy.  
We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You are advised to check it from time to time in order to ensure that you are aware of any changes and that they are acceptable to you. For changes to this privacy policy that we consider to be material, we will place a notice on the Website by revising the link on the homepage to read substantially as "Updated Privacy Policy" for a reasonable amount of time. The most current version of this privacy policy will be available on the Website and will supersede all previous versions of this privacy policy. Continued use of the Services will signify that you agree to any such changes. Please see the top of this policy for the date the policy was last updated. This policy applies if you access the Service through your mobile phone, through your PC or through any other route.

What information do we collect about you?  
In general, you can view parts of the Website without giving us any information. On certain pages we will request information about you, for example, the registration pages. We will only be able to provide you with our full Website environment and Service features if you have completed and submitted the information required for the registration process and this is accepted by us in accordance with our Website terms and conditions.   
Some of the information that we collect will be 'Personal Data.' This means data related to you and which identifies you. In this policy, we use the terms 'Personal Data' and 'information about you' interchangeably.   
Beyond the information you give to us, we automatically receive and record on our server logs other types of information when you use the Service, including the location of your mobile device, IP address, cookie information, the page(s) you request and other usage information. We treat this data as non-Personal Data, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law.   
What do we do with your information?  
We may use information about you for any of the following purposes:  
to register you on our Website, to administer our Service and Website features (including processing any searches or requests for information about our products or services), and to allow you to use those services (e.g. blogs, open forums and discussion pages);  
for assessment and analysis of our market, customers, products and services (including asking you for your opinions on our products and services and carrying out customer surveys);  
to enable us to monitor, review and improve the products and services which we offer;  
for internal record keeping;  
(subject to the direct marketing section below) for marketing purposes;  
to conduct free prize draws, prize competitions, or promotions; and  
to consider employing you if you have provided information pursuant to an application for a position with us.  
We reserve the right to share all Personal Data and non-Personal Data with any company within the Samsung Electronics group of companies, or with any other company that operates under the Samsung brand (each, a "Samsung Group Company", and collectively, the "Samsung Group Companies"). A list of the Samsung Group Companies is available upon request. Each of the Samsung Group Companies will use your information in accordance with their own independent privacy practices. 

How do we collect the information?  
We collect information about you using various active and passive methods, including:  
when you submit it through the Website; and  
when you telephone or email us, or correspond with us by means other than through this Website.  
We may combine information that we collect about you through this Website with information that you provide to us by other means, or that is provided to us by third parties. We may store that information together in a combined database or in separate databases.   
Our goal is to retain information about you only for so long as is necessary for the purpose for which it was intended, or as required under any contract or by law (and we will usually delete data once a user tells us that that he/she will no longer be using this Service). We strive not to collect an excessive amount of information from you or information that is not relevant to the purposes for it was collected.

What about anonymous information?  
We may automatically collect technical information from which you cannot be identified when you connect to this Website or use the Service. An example is the domain name of another website from which you linked to this Website. We collect this information to help us with identifying users' browsing preferences. The information is used for internal purposes so that we can carry out research on your demographics, behaviour and interests. Anonymous or generic information from which you cannot be personally identified is not Personal Data and is therefore outside the scope of this policy.

What about location-based services?  
To the extent that you are using any of our location-based services or functionality ("Location-Based Services"), then in addition to the terms of this Privacy Policy, this Clause will also apply. The Location-Based Services are offered by collecting, storing, transmitting or processing location data of the user and/or his or her Samsung device upon consenting to the use of such Location-Based Services. This information is anonymous and does not personally identify you although the information may be combined with your personal information in order for us to provide you with Location-Based Services, such as Remote Locator and Phone Tracking. All such information that is Personal Data will be dealt with in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy.

To whom do we disclose your information?  
We will not disclose to any third parties Personal Data which relates to you without your consent, except:   
to a Samsung Group Company;  
where it is necessary to enable any of our staff, employees, agents, contractors, suppliers or commercial partners to provide a service to us or to perform a function on our behalf (including providing marketing assistance, market research or customer services; and administering your membership, supplying products or services that we provide to you now or in the future, or any free prize draws, prize competitions or promotions);   
to our professional advisers or where we are under a duty to disclose your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation or the decision of a judicial authority;  
to the purchaser or potential purchaser of our rights and obligations relating to this Service and/or the Website (in which case personal data held by us about our customers will be a transferred asset of any purchase) we may transfer your personal information to that third party; or  
where it is necessary in order to pursue our legitimate interests or if we are required to or are permitted to do so by law.  
You acknowledge that any information that you submit into any environment that is visible to others (e.g. blogs, forums and discussion pages) will result in such information being published in like manner. You should take common sense precautions about the information you provide in such environments and acknowledge that your information will be published in such a way for others to see.  
For any disclosure of your Personal Data by us to a carefully selected third party or to any third party on the above list, we will comply with data protection law by ensuring that there are arrangements in place to ensure that the third party does not use your Personal Data for any purpose other than in accordance with this policy, and that they will keep it secure. Should you wish to object to such disclosure, please opt-out by contacting us at the address below.   
To the extent permitted by law, Samsung does not represent or warrant that the Service, or any part thereof, is appropriate or available for use in any specific jurisdiction. Those who choose to access the Service do so on their own initiative and at their own risk, and are responsible for complying with all local laws, rules and regulations. If you reside in the European Economic Area ("EEA"), please note that we may disclose your Personal Data to a Samsung Group Company or a third party which is outside the EEA for the purposes described in this policy. The data protection laws outside the EEA may not provide an equivalent level of protection to those in your home country, however before transferring the data we will take steps to ensure that your Personal Data will be afforded the same level of protection as that required from us by data protection law. We do not sell or make available your personal information to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes except as provided herein.  
We will take all reasonable precautions to ensure that our staff and employees who have access to information about you have received adequate training to ensure that they process that information only in accordance with this policy and with our obligations under data protection law. We may take disciplinary action against our staff and employees in the event of non-compliance, should we consider this to be appropriate.

Direct Marketing  
We may use information about you which we hold in order to provide you with information about products, promotions, and other such information which we believe may be of interest to you if you select to receive such information by email and/or post when you complete the registration process.   
You can change your mind about your preferences in respect of direct marketing by using the unsubscribe information on every such mailing or by updating your user profile. You can do this at any time. If you do so, we would not remove your Personal Data from our database(s) to the extent that it is still required by us under the terms of this privacy policy but we would note your changed preferences as soon as reasonably possible.

Accessing your information  
Under certain data protection laws you may have the right to request details of Personal Data which we hold about you. If we are permitted by law, we may charge you a small fee for providing you with that information. If you would like to make any such request please contact our customer service department at the Help menu of the Website.  
Please help us to ensure that the information about you that we hold is accurate and up to date. If you think that any information we have about you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to our customer service department in the manner set out above. We will correct or update any information about you as soon as reasonably possible.

What do we do to keep your information secure?  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to do so, we have put in place reasonable physical, technical and organisational measures and procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect through the website. This has been done with a view to preventing unauthorised or unlawful processing of your Personal Data and accidental, unauthorised or unlawful access, use, processing, copying, alteration, transfer, loss or destruction of, or damage to, your Personal Data. Whilst we have done all of this, no website, internet transmission, computer system or wireless connection is completely secure. Samsung cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss or other breaches will never occur.  
We protect the security of your information by:  
using encryption where appropriate;  
using password protection where appropriate; and  
limiting access to your information (for example, only our staff or employees who need access to it for the purposes described above will have access to it).   
You must also take appropriate steps to keep your information secure by not using an obvious login name or password, by changing your password regularly, and ensuring that you do not divulge your password to any other person.

Linking  
This Website may link to other websites which are outside our control. Whilst we try to ensure that we link only to websites that share our privacy and security standards, once you have left this Website we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide on other websites. You should exercise caution, and review the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for those policies.

Cookies and web beacons  
We use cookies for certain areas of our Website. Cookies are files that store information on your hard drive or browser. They enable this Website to recognise that you have visited it before. Cookies help us to understand which sections of this Website are the most popular because they allow us to see which pages visitors are accessing and how much time they are spending on them. By studying these we are better able to adapt this Website to suit your demands and provide you with a more customised user experience. For example, cookies allow us to ensure that the information displayed on your next visit to this Website will match up with your user preferences.  
You may configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is sent. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. For example, on Microsoft Internet Explorer, you can disable or delete cookies by selecting "Tools/Internet Options" and reviewing your privacy settings or selecting "delete cookies". Please note, however, that this Website is designed to work using cookies and any disabling of them may affect your usage of this Website and prevent you from taking full advantage of it. We do not exchange cookies with any third party websites or external data suppliers, except with third parties working with us to provide services to you.  
The Website and/or the Service may enable the use of the Adobe Flash Player. By default, your use of the Adobe Flash Player generates flash cookies. Adobe provides a short disclosure about Flash Cookies in its End User License Agreement, stating "Use of the web players, specifically the Flash Player, will enable the Software to store certain user settings as a local shared object on our computer. These settings are not associated with you, but allow you to configure certain settings within the Flash Player.” The Adobe Flash Player (and similar applications) use flash cookies to remember user settings, preferences and usage similar to the browser cookies referenced above, but flash cookies can store more information than browser cookies and are managed through a different interface than the one provided by your web browser. You can control the degree to which you accept flash cookies by accessing your Adobe Flash Player management tools directly through the settings manager for Adobe Flash, located at http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html. If you do not allow flash cookies to take any disc space on your computer, you may not be able to take advantage of or participate in certain features on the Service and/or Website. The Adobe Flash Player is not the only technology that may be used by us or otherwise in the ever-shifting online and mobile content environment. HTML5 is an increasingly popular web standard used for presenting content, especially content delivered to mobile devices. HTML is the mark-up language used for the World Wide Web. Some HTML5 code may allow your response to advertising and other activities to be monitored across websites and such information to be stored on your computer or mobile device. Technology solutions that allow users to opt-out of or block this sort of tracking are being developed through browser add-ons and other tools.

This Website and the communications generated from using and/or registering on this Website, such as promotional emails, may contain electronic images known as "web beacons". Web beacons generally work in conjunction with cookies, and we may use them in the same way we use cookies (see above).  
Further information

If you have any specific questions, then contact us at:

Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd,   
416, Maetan-3dong, Yeongtong-gu, Suwon-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea   
Email: account.cs@samsung.com

2012-05-29
